<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<activity id="2012" moduleid="8991" modulename="label" contextid="57239">
  <label id="2012">
    <name>


Welcome to&amp;nbsp;Building a Bridge to Adult C...</name>
    <intro>&lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 style="font-style: italic;"&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/ACP%20Training%20Series.png" alt="The 3 courses in the ACP Training Series are (1) Engaging Stakeholders (2) Contextualized Instruction and (3) Bridge Programs" width="400" height="311" class="img-responsive atto_image_button_right"&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 style=""&gt;&lt;strong style=""&gt;Welcome to&amp;nbsp;Building a Bridge to Adult Career Pathways!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p style="font-style: italic;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This course and the accompanying materials were developed by Debra Jones, Ed.D., in collaboration with the American Institutes for Research.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="font-style: italic;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=""&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;This course will take about 3 hours to complete.&amp;nbsp;Please note, items with solid boxes can be self-checked to indicate completion; however, the self-assessment and all learning checks are graded and required for completion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=""&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;It is one in a series
of three self-directed courses focusing on adult career pathways and is
intended for local program administrators. However, state directors, department
chairs, deans, academic senates, career development staff, curriculum
developers, and other education, workforce, and community professionals will
benefit from understanding how this course supports the design of bridge
programs and the alignment of curriculum and employment outcomes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer:&amp;nbsp;Please note the LINCS System is maintained under contract with CivicActions with funding from the U.S. Department of Education (ED), Office of Career, Technical, and Adult Education (OCTAE), under Contract No. ED-EVP-O-16-F-0001. The opinions expressed herein do not necessarily represent the positions or policies of the U.S. Department of Education, and no official endorsement by the U.S. Department of Education should be inferred.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</intro>
    <introformat>1</introformat>
    <timemodified>1646076459</timemodified>
  </label>
</activity>